mrtweet.net 2011-06-25

# Privacy | Lytro

#### (effective June 21, 2011)

Lytro, Inc. ("Lytro," "we" or "us") provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of www.lytro.com. This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through our website. Our Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time, and we will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on our website.

  1. The Information We Collect

    * In the course of using this website, you may provide us with personally identifiable information. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you and information on your use of and activities at our website that may be connected with you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information that we collect may include, but is not limited to, your name and email address. Personal Information may also include information you supply to us concerning your preferences and interests expressed in the course of use of our website.
    * You also can engage with our content on or through third-party social networking sites (such as Facebook) or third-party social media plug-ins and applications. In such cases, you may allow us to have access to certain information from your social media profile (for example, name, e-mail address, photo, gender, birthday, location, your list of friends, people you follow and/or who follow you, and the posts or the 'likes' you make) to deliver the content or as part of the operation of the application. We may also obtain non-personally identifiable information (for example, content viewed) from your interaction with our content.
    * When you visit our website, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This information may include, but is not limited to, your computer’s Internet Protocol address, browser type, the web page you were visiting before you came to our website, and information you search for on our website. Like many websites, we also use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use “persistent cookies” to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to our website. We use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of our website, to better understand how you interact with the Site, and to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on our website. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of our website or all functionality of our services.
  2. How We Use Personal Information

We use information that we obtain through our website in the following ways:

    * Personal Information is used for the following purposes: 1) to improve our website, products, services, features and content, 2) to administer your use of our website, 3) to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate our website, 4) to verify your membership in social networking websites, and 5) if you have provided us with your email address, to send you marketing and/or research communications. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.
    * We use information we obtain by technical means (such as the automatic recording performed by our servers or through the use of cookies) for the above purposes and in order to monitor and analyze use of our website and our services and for our website’s technical administration, to increase our website’s functionality and user-friendliness, to better tailor it to your needs, to generate and derive useful data and information concerning the interests, characteristics and website use behavior of our users, and to verify that visitors to our website meet the criteria required to process their requests. 
    * We may on occasion combine information we collect through our website with information that we collect from other sources.
  3. Information Sharing and Disclosure

We may share information that we obtain through our website with:

Service Providers, Business Partners, and Others. We may employ third-party companies and individuals to facilitate our service, to provide the service on our behalf, to perform website-related services (including but not limited to maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of our website’s features), to assist us in communicating with you, or to assist us in analyzing how our website and service are used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only for purposes of performing these tasks on our behalf. We may also provide Personal Information to our business partners or other entities with which we have cooperative relationships so that they can send you promotional and other information and engage in any of the activities described in Section 2 above.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement. We also may disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or if we believe that disclosure is necessary to (i) comply with the law or with legal process, (ii) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website, products, or services, or (iii) protect the personal safety or property of users of our website, services, the public or Lytro and its employees. 

Business Transfers. We may sell, transfer, or otherwise share some or all of our assets, including Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization, or sale of assets, or in the event of bankruptcy.

  4. Security 

Safeguarding your information is important to us. We employ reasonable measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access.

  5. Information from Children

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at legal@lytro.com. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files. 

  6. Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites

Our sites may contain links to or integrations with other sites such as Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, etc., whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

  7. Contacting Us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at legal@lytro.com or Privacy Officer, c/o Lytro, Inc., 200 W. Evelyn Avenue, Suite 120, Mountain View, CA 94041.
